{
    "subject": "Artie_Lange",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Artie_Lange's_Beer_League",
    "human_readable": "Artie Lange created Artie Lange's Beer League.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9874995350837708,
            "question": "Who created Artie Lange's Beer League?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9395824670791626,
            "question": "What kind of show is Artie Lange's Beer League?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9380890727043152,
            "question": "How has Artie Lange's career influenced the creation of his Beer League show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9010978937149048,
            "question": "What topics might be covered on Artie Lange's Beer League?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8903259038925171,
            "question": "Who are some other comedians who might appear on Artie Lange's Beer League?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.842972457408905,
            "question": "Has Artie Lange's Beer League won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8219585418701172,
            "question": "What makes Artie Lange's Beer League unique compared to other comedy shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7996466159820557,
            "question": "Where can you watch episodes of Artie Lange's Beer League?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.686517596244812,
            "question": "What is the name of the show created by Artie Lange?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6371439695358276,
            "question": "Is Artie Lange involved in the creation of his own show?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Artie Lange created Artie Lange's Beer League.",
            "html": "yago_26119_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the show created by Artie Lange?",
            "html": "yago_26119_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you watch episodes of Artie Lange's Beer League?",
            "html": "yago_26119_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Artie Lange's Beer League unique compared to other comedy shows?",
            "html": "yago_26119_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26119_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26119_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26119_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26119_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26119_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26119_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26119_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26119_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26119_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26119_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because there is no mention of Artie Lange creating Artie Lange's Beer League in any of the documents. The information provided only talks about Artie Lange starring in and hosting various events related to the film, but does not mention him as its creator."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Artie Lange starring in and creating the film \"Artie Lange's Beer League,\" which supports the statement that Artie Lange created the movie with that title."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}